OpenHands CLI Primitives. High-level
commands for demo recording.
Recording OpenHands CLI demos used to
require complex keystroke sequences.
Manual typing, waiting for startup, timing
AI responses.
Now demorec supports high-level
primitives. Install, Start, Prompt,
WaitForReady, and Quit. Each handles the
complexity internally.
Here's an example script. One line per
action. No keystroke details to worry
about.
Let's see it in action.
First, let's look at this demo script.
Notice the openhands submode and the
high-level commands.
The Install command runs uv tool install
openhands.
Start launches the CLI and waits for it to
be ready.
Prompt sends our message to the AI.
WaitForReady polls the terminal until the
You: prompt appears.
The AI responded. WaitForReady detected
when it was done.
Finally, Quit exits the CLI cleanly.
OpenHands CLI Primitives. Available now in
demorec. Check out the repo and try it on
your next demo.