When creating demos, you often need
multiple terminals and mode switches.
Previously, you'd lose all terminal state.
Let me show you how persistent sessions
fix this.
We've set up our working directory and
environment. Now let's start a web server
in a separate terminal.
This is a named session called 'server'.
It's completely independent.
Server is running. Let's see it in the
browser.
The page loads from our server.
Now from a separate client terminal:
Client fetches the same content.
Back to the server terminal. Notice the
request logs - the session persisted.
And our original default terminal? Still
has its state from the beginning.
Working directory and environment
variables intact across all those mode
switches!
That's persistent sessions and named
sessions - complex multi-terminal demos
made simple.