demorec. Proof of work that's easy on the
eye.
AI agents are writing more code than ever.
Reviewers need evidence that changes
actually work. Video is easy to consume,
but time-consuming to produce.
Demorec produces short video demos from
scripts that execute real commands.
Because the script runs the actual
code—especially in CI without human
influence—the evidence is hard to fake.
In this demo, we'll walk through this
script in vim, start a web server, view
the page in the browser, and return to
terminal to see the request logs.
Let's look at the script that's producing
this video.
At the top, we set the output file,
dimensions, and voice for narration.
Here we switch to presentation mode and
show slides.
Then we switch to terminal mode. This is
where we open vim to show this very
script.
Next, we switch to browser mode to
navigate to a web page.
And back to terminal to see the server
logs. Mode switches are seamless.
Now let's see it in action. We'll start a
server.
And view it in the browser.
The page loads. This is real—the server is
actually running.
Back to the terminal—you can see the
request in the server logs.
Every mode switch, every command, every
page load—it all actually executes.
When recording finishes, you get an MP4
and subtitles.
The reviewer watches 30 seconds instead of
reading 200 lines of code.
Demorec. Proof of work that's easy on the
eye. Check out the repo and try it on your
next PR.