Let's look at the script powering this
demo.
The header sets output file, dimensions,
and voice.
Here's the magic—the at-offscreen
directive. Everything below it runs but is
NOT recorded.
This creates a terminal session called
joke one and echoes a dad joke. The viewer
never sees this happen.
Same for joke two—another named session,
another joke, all invisible to the viewer.
And joke three. Three terminal sessions,
three dad jokes, zero video footage.
Then at-onscreen starts the recording.
From here on, everything goes into the
video.
Later in the script, we switch back to
each joke terminal. The jokes are already
there—pre-loaded during offscreen setup.
Joke one was set up offscreen. You never
saw it happen, but here it is.
Joke two, same story. Prepared in advance,
revealed on cue.
And joke three. All the setup happened
before you started watching.
Offscreen directives let you prepare
everything before the camera rolls.
Install dependencies, start servers,
pre-load pages—all invisible to viewers.
Welcome to cleaner demos.